Jakub Aniszewski

Software Engineer

Hello! My name is Kuba Aniszewski. Based in Wroclaw, Poland -I am Software Engineer with 2+ years of experience (in testing). Currently I work as a Software Engineer in Test. In my free time, I work on side projects and learn more about web development.



Work Experience

"... tietoevcy

Software **Engineer in Test**

Nov 2022 - Present

Project for Renesas Electronics focused on testing Bluetooth Low Energy SDK. Automation of tests cases with Robot Framework and

MOSIA

Software **Engineer in Test**

Jul 2021 - Oct 2022

Python Working Student

Jan 2020 - Jun 2021

Hands-on experience in 5G BTS software testing, in the security domain. I used Python, Robot Framework, and Selenium to automate tests and reported bugs with JIRA. Proficient in Linux, I played a key role in the CI/CD processes. I also maintained regression tests for the team. Additionally, I led the development of a side project web application using Python, Django, React, and Docker. This project boosted our team's productivity by about 60%.

Projects

LinkVerse July 2023

9 🐌

Streamer Spotlight June 2023

→ 😂 🌖

A web app for rating streamers, built with NestJS and MongoDB on the backend and React on the frontend. Features include streamer bios, platform info, content descriptions, and a like/dislike system.

An app made with SvelteKit that puts all your

profiles and content into one shareable link.

authentication. Features customizable profiles

Utilizes Firebase for real-time data and

Personal Portfolio & Blog

August 2023

A ~

Ø Visit aniszewski.dev!

A simple website which shows achievements, projects, and skills. It's made with Astro and includes a blog for industry tips. Tailwind CSS ensures intuitive design and navigation.

Education

Master's Degree in Computer Science

Wroclaw University of Technology 2021 - 2023

Bachelor's Degree in

Computer Science Wroclaw University of Technology 2017 - 2021

IT Technician

Opole Electrical Schools Complex 2013 - 2017

Skills

Python

TupeScript

React

Contact Info



+48 692 706 767



jakubaniszewski@pm.me



www.aniszewski.dev